<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HeHe Script❤️</title>
    <link>https://hehe-font.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on HeHe Script❤️</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hehe-font.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ROUGHNESS</title>
      <link>https://hehe-font.github.io/projects/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hehe-font.github.io/projects/photography/</guid>
      <description>TRUE SCRIPTING EFFECT Roughness effect gives an authentic handwritten finish. A cleaner outline and smaller character set is also available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RICH VARIANTS</title>
      <link>https://hehe-font.github.io/projects/design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hehe-font.github.io/projects/design/</guid>
      <description>A balance between regularisation and randomness when creating alternative characters. As you type a letter, each one of the three variants appears in an order that avoids repetition of the same shape, making it appear random.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi-lingual</title>
      <link>https://hehe-font.github.io/projects/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hehe-font.github.io/projects/writing/</guid>
      <description>The addition of diacritical characters to cover Latin alphabets means it’s ready to take on broader challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://hehe-font.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 13:19:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hehe-font.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always been obsessed with hand writing. Shortly after listening to a talk given by Toshi Omagari on how he made Sir Quentin Blake typeface, it immediately struck me with the gerund of my friend Hehe&amp;rsquo;s journal as it always gave me a sense of tender &amp;amp; vigor.
I spent my last three days carefully crafting these lovely characters and here it is. Thank you Hehe for allowing me to replicate her journal as a typeface and every single friendly and gifted individual at type school :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Type School Diary</title>
      <link>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/type-diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 11:58:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/type-diary/</guid>
      <description>#TypeSchool by @3type_cn
- DAY ONE - wrote some calligraphy, watched some Hamilton [sic], traced some roman letters, wasted some food.
- DAY TWO - quick type sketches, critiques, fake Japanese food, then we hugged good bye to adorkable Toshi.
- DAY THREE - more calligraphy, more quick sketches, more type knowledge, getting more serious 🤔
- DAY FOUR - latin is not enough.
- DAY FIVE - starting to draw sketches for the final assignment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seal Life</title>
      <link>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/seal-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 12:04:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/seal-life/</guid>
      <description>We all love seal!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Ipsum</title>
      <link>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/startup-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 12:04:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/startup-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>SpaceTeam affordances quantitative vs. qualitative SpaceTeam physical computing earned media thinker-maker-doer pair programming. Bootstrapping pitch deck physical computing driven cortado human-centered design innovate human-centered design driven. Grok pitch deck fund pitch deck sticky note affordances minimum viable product integrate paradigm viral iterate. Driven fund thought leader personas workflow SpaceTeam viral pair programming physical computing intuitive 360 campaign latte bootstrapping minimum viable product. Bootstrapping physical computing responsive pitch deck SpaceTeam parallax long shadow pitch deck bootstrapping ideate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://hehe-font.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 13:23:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hehe-font.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Currently this font is still under development. If you wish to get the latest version , you can drop me an email. I should be able to reply every evening =)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>