<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on HeHe Script 🍰</title>
    <link>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on HeHe Script 🍰</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 14:26:17 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi Lingual</title>
      <link>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/multi-lingual/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 14:26:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/multi-lingual/</guid>
      <description>We support 30 languages! The following is the complete list. The text is adapted from list of pangrams.
English
These violent delights have violent ends.
Breton
Yec’hed mat Jakez ! Skarzhit ar gwerennoù-mañ, kavet e vo gwin betek fin ho puhez
Catalan
«Dóna amor que seràs feliç!».Això, il·lús company geniüt, ja és un lluït rètol blavís d’onze kWh.
Gojazni
đačić s biciklom drži hmelj i finu vatu u džepu nošnje.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Type School Diary</title>
      <link>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/type-diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 11:58:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/type-diary/</guid>
      <description>credit: all content and images belong to typeschool and 3type
#TypeSchool by @3type_cn
- DAY ONE - wrote some calligraphy, watched some Hamilton [sic], traced some roman letters, wasted some food.
- DAY TWO - quick type sketches, critiques, fake Japanese food, then we hugged good bye to adorkable Toshi.
- DAY THREE - more calligraphy, more quick sketches, more type knowledge, getting more serious 🤔
- DAY FOUR - latin is not enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seal Life</title>
      <link>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/seal-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 12:04:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/seal-life/</guid>
      <description>We all love seal!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Ipsum</title>
      <link>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/startup-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 12:04:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hehe-font.github.io/blog/startup-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>SpaceTeam affordances quantitative vs. qualitative SpaceTeam physical computing earned media thinker-maker-doer pair programming. Bootstrapping pitch deck physical computing driven cortado human-centered design innovate human-centered design driven. Grok pitch deck fund pitch deck sticky note affordances minimum viable product integrate paradigm viral iterate. Driven fund thought leader personas workflow SpaceTeam viral pair programming physical computing intuitive 360 campaign latte bootstrapping minimum viable product. Bootstrapping physical computing responsive pitch deck SpaceTeam parallax long shadow pitch deck bootstrapping ideate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>